(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-04T23:27:01.113293",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will start soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
秘密結社holoX 1st Live「FIRST MISSION」
Secret Society holoX 1st Live: FIRST MISSION
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will start soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
秘密結社holoX 1st Live「FIRST MISSION」
Secret Society holoX 1st Live: FIRST MISSION
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will begin shortly.
演出の都合上、照明の明滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is allowed.
どアニメ宣言！
Do-Anime Sengen!
アニメにハマって歌いたくなっちゃった！
I got hooked on anime, and now I want to sing!
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて...
Singing karaoke while watching my favorite scenes...
尊すぎてつらい！
It's so precious, it hurts!
歌いたいアニメ・ゲームソング見つけよう！
Let's find the anime and game songs you want to sing!
JOYSOUND
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will start soon.
演出の都合上、照明の明滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights. / Cheering loudly is OK.
本日は
Today...
みなさん！ホロックスライブ
Everyone! Welcome to HoloX Live
2024 ファーストミッションに
2024 First Mission!
ご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming today!
自己紹介！
Self-introductions!
注目せよ！
Attention, please!
吾輩の名は、ラプラス・ダークネスだ！
My name is Laplus Darknesss!
皆さん、お待たせ。
Everyone, sorry to keep you waiting.
秘密結社holoXの女幹部、鷹嶺ルイと申します。
I am Takane Lui, the executive officer of Secret Society holoX.
皆、こんこよー！
Everyone, Konkoyo!
秘密結社holoXの頭脳、博衣こよりだよー！
I'm Hakui Koyori, the brains of Secret Society holoX!
沙花叉はー？
What about Sakamata?
カット！
Cut!
おー、よくできたわ！
Wow, well done!
ホロックスの掃除屋、インターン、お掃除＆飼育員担当、沙花叉クロヱでございます。
I am Sakamata Chloe, the cleaner, intern, and cleaning/custodian officer of holoX!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます！
To ensure everyone enjoys the live show to the very end, we have a few announcements!
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機器の使用は、固くお断りいたします！
Photography, recording, and filming during the performance are strictly prohibited!
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせず、お近くのスタッフへお知らせください！
If you feel unwell, do not push yourself and please inform a nearby staff member!
いい子です。
Good. You're being very good.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、
Actions such as moshing, diving, jumping excessively,
ステージに物を投げ込むなど、他のお客様のご迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
throwing objects onto the stage, or any other acts that disrupt the show or bother others are strictly prohibited.
また、3階と4階の最前列席は、危険防止のため、立ち見禁止です。
Additionally, standing is strictly prohibited in the front rows of the 3rd and 4th floors to prevent danger.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね。
Please follow the rules and have a great time.
お守りいただけない場合、ご退場いただく可能性がございます。
If you do not comply, you may be asked to leave.
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合がございます。
Also, cameras for video streaming and photography are in the venue today, so the audience may be captured.
これらの映像や写真は、プロモーションなどに使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください！
Please note that these videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
いい返事でござる！
That's a good answer!
また、ライブのハッシュタグは、ハッシュタグ「SSホロックス世界再描画計画」です！
Also, the hashtag for today's live is #SSHoloXWorldRepaintProject !
ハッシュタグを使って、たくさんたくさん盛り上げてください！
Please use the hashtag and post a lot to build up the excitement!
それでは、開演までもう少しです！
Well then, there are only a few moments left before the show starts!
みんなで一緒に盛り上がるでござる！
Let's all get excited together!
みんな、しーっ...
Everyone, shh...
静かに...
Quietly...
そこへ跪け！
Kneel down right there!
吐いて捨てるような現実を
This reality that you would spit out and discard...
一刀両断 叩き斬る
I shall slice it in half with a single stroke!
終わりなき輪廻に迷いし子らよ
Oh, children lost in endless reincarnation...
漆黒の翼で誘おう
Let me guide you with pitch-black wings.
我らエデンの星を統べる者、秘密結社…
We who rule the Planet of Eden, Secret Society...
holoX！！
holoX!!
で、ござる～！
...de gozaru~!
ウォッ オー ウォッ オッ オッ オー オー オー
Woah oh, woah oh oh oh oh oh...
how low？
How low?
どうしようもないこの世界
In this hopeless world of ours...
（どうして欲しい？）
(What do you want me to do?)
black out
終末告げる鐘が鳴る
The bell tolls to announce the end.
ラッパッパッパ ラ
Rap-pap-pap-pa ra!
パって踊ろうぜ tripしようぜ
Let's dance in a flash, let's take a trip.
陰キャも陽キャも sing a song
Both introverts and extroverts, sing a song!
気持ちいいことだけが すべて
Feeling good is all that matters.
堕ちていく 闇の底へ
Falling down to the bottom of darkness.
甘い 甘い メロディ
A sweet, sweet melody.
ほら どうぞ どうぞ 手の鳴る方へ
Come on, this way, towards the clapping hands.
もう 逃げられない ほら 闇に染まれば
You can't escape anymore, see, once you're stained in darkness.
世界を塗り替えろ 望めばくれてやろう すべて
Repaint the world, if you wish for it, I'll give you everything.
hololive production presents.
holoX Live 2026 "First Mission"
秘密結社holoX 総帥 ラプラス・ダークネス
Secret Society holoX Leader: La+ Darknesss
秘密結社holoX 幹部 鷹嶺ルイ
Secret Society holoX Executive: Takane Lui
秘密結社holoX 研究者 博衣こより
Secret Society holoX Researcher: Hakui Koyori
秘密結社holoX 用心棒 風真いろは
Secret Society holoX Bodyguard: Kazama Iroha
我ら、エデンの星を統べる者、秘密結社...
We, the rulers of Eden, Secret Society...
holoX!
参る！
Here we come!
時は満ちた。
The time has come.
共鳴より現れし、眷属共よ！
My minions, summoned by resonance!
準備はいいかー！
Are you ready?!
行くぞ！
Let's go!
Are you ready?
Dap pa pa, dap pa dap pa dap pa
dap pa, dap pa dap pa dap pa, rap pa
Yes!
Dap pa pa, dap pa dap pa dap pa
dap pa, dap pa dap pa dap pa, rap pa
夜が深まる ほら Darkness
The night deepens, look, there is Darkness
脳に手枷をはめて隠す
Binding our minds with shackles to hide them
何したってええよ エゴイスティック
Do whatever you want, you egoist
忍に忍忍 サムライガール
Stealthily, nin-nin, samurai girl
読み切れないけど
Even if we can't fully foresee it...
フルベトでしょ？ Shaking Shaking
It's Frubeto, right? Shaking, Shaking
手探るゲーム
In this fumbling game...
鮮やかに赤字 Jacking Jacking
Vividly red-inked, Jacking, Jacking
悪の手のひら
In the palm of evil...
踊りたくなって
...making you want to dance...
お望みに
...just as you desired...
気づけば ノリノリです！
...and before you know it, we're rocking it!
どうしようもない
There's no helping it,
there's no helping it.
宇宙的運命
It's our cosmic destiny.
なんか しょうがない
Somehow, it can't be avoided,
全部 塗り替えよう
so let's repaint it all!
X と X と X と X が
When X, X, X, and X...
交差する真ん中で
...intersect right in the center,
Next と Next と Next と世界は
with Next, Next, and Next, the world...
もう始まってる
...has already begun!
JUMP!
Woah...
飛びな！飛びな！
Jump! Jump!
神が呼ぶ方へ
To where God calls us!
Woah...
阿吽の呼吸
With perfect sync!
Xです！
It is X!
混沌としたこの世界を、我らholoX色に塗り替えるのだ！
We shall repaint this chaotic world in our holoX colors!
皆の者、かかれ！
Everyone, charge!
Yes, My Dark!
Absolute Darkness...
Infinity!
エデンの星は、我が手中に！
The planet Eden is in my hands!
Dap pa pa, dap pa dap pa dap pa
dap pa, dap pa dap pa dap pa, rap pa
風穴は開けたんだ
I've blasted a wind tunnel open!
支配は始まった
Our reign has begun!
息はもうかけたの バズゾーンの
I've already breathed life into the buzz zone,
近くにいるはずよ
so it must be close by.
抑えきれない 自力制御不能のパワー
This uncontrollable, self-governing power...
捕まえてみなよ 影も形もない My Heart
...try to catch my shadowless, shapeless heart!
Absolute Darkness is Love
剥ぎ剥ぎ出すアプリオリの
Stripping away the a priori......and following your heart!
心に従って
...and following your heart!
忠誠示してよ 今こそ
Show your loyalty, right now!
Baby, let me down!
Dap pa pa, dap pa dap pa dap pa
dap pa, dap pa dap pa dap pa, rap pa
絡みつきミクステイになるでしょう
We'll probably entangle and become a mixture
Dap pa pa, dap pa dap pa dap pa
dap pa, dap pa dap pa dap pa, rap pa
並ぶ切り札 足りてないのよ
The trump cards lined up are not enough,
Yes, Toughなエンジェルでしょう
yes, you must be a tough angel.
革命的存在を射る
Shooting down the revolutionary existence,
Cost-playの重大感情
the serious feelings of cosplay...
吹き去って
...blow them away!
Dap pa pa...
drop candy
我が名は 鷹嶺ルイ！お前もホロックスの一員となるのだ！
My name is Lui Takane! You too shall become a member of holoX!
So when... Do you want?
...till you remember me?
ちょっと目が合ったとき 散らばったナイトメアも
When our eyes met for a moment, even the scattered nightmares...
真っ赤っかさ それはウィンク
...turned bright red. That's a wink.
ウィンク ウィンク 目が合ってもずっとラッキー
Wink, wink, even if our eyes meet, I'm always lucky.
I'm flirtatious. My type の目... ウィンク
I'm flirtatious. The eyes of my type... Wink.
ちょっとお目が高い 目に入れたって痛くないくらい
You've got quite an eye! So cute that it wouldn't hurt even if I put you in it.
ララララ口走るニュースペーパーに
La-la-la-la, babbling in the newspaper.
憎しみはとうに捨てた。怖がってんの？ふーん、あっそ
I abandoned hatred long ago. Are you scared? Hmph, whatever.
Don't let me down
まだまだダウン
Still going down.
安全じゃないから 健全じゃないから
Because it's not safe, because it's not wholesome,
それが何だってんだ フロンティア
...what of it? This is the frontier.
誰 目には目を
An eye for an eye, for whoever it is.
ウィンク 知らないなら見せつけるわ
Wink, if you don't know it, I'll show it to you,
君へウィンク 知りたいなら"
...a wink just for you. If you want to know,
真っ赤っかさ Oh 愛愛愛
...it'll turn bright red. Oh, love, love, love...
I want you でバイバイバイさ
...with an "I want you", it's bye-bye-bye.
目に物見せるマイン
I'll show you what I'm made of.
いいよ、目を瞑る半分ね ほら、ウィンク
It's fine, close half of your eyes. Look, wink.
ウィンク
Wink.
ほら、目を瞑る半分に
Look, close half of your eyes...
愛をあげるよ。ウィンク
...and I'll give you love. Wink.
はーい、マッドサイエンティストの
Hi! I'm the mad scientist...
博衣こよりです！これで君も助手くんだね！
...Hakui Koyori! Now you are my assistant!
はーい、みんなの脳みそに お注射しちゃうぞー！
Now, I'm going to inject everyone's brains!
ジッケンタ！ジッケンタ！ジッケンジッケンジッケンタ！
Test subject! Test subject! Test-test-test subject!
ジッケンタ！ジッケンタ！一緒に！わっふー！
Test subject! Test subject! Together! Wah-hoo!
ジッケンタ！ジッケンタ！ジッケンジッケンジッケンタ！ジッケンタ！ジッケンタ！ジッケンタ！
Test subject! Test subject! Test-test-test subject! Test subject!
てきゅーてきゅーてきゅー！ てきゅーてきゅー処方中！
Thank you, thank you, thank you! Thank you, thank you, now prescribing!
予防接種もインフルエンザも ピーポーピーポーピーポー！
Vaccinations and the flu, pee-poo-pee-poo-pee-poo!
検証！検証！検証！ テンション上げてポイっ！
Verify! Verify! Verify! Raise your tension and toss it!
舐めてたら火傷しちゃうよ？
If you underestimate me, you'll get burned!
迷ったらダメダメ！ 迷ったらサイエンス！
Don't hesitate! If you hesitate, choose science!
迷いも悩みもマヨマヨ中！
Doubt and worries are all in a muddle!
こよりのデザインと こよりのハッピー！
Koyori's design and Koyori's happy!
こより、こよりだけで恋い焦がれ！
Yearning for Koyori, and Koyori alone!
サイン、コサイン、タンジェント！ 執着心、独占欲、大爆発！
Sine, cosine, tangent! Obsession and possessiveness exploding!
脳内マシーンがドカン！
The machine in my brain goes bang!
天才！天才！天才！ 飛んでみなくちゃエンド！
Genius! Genius! Genius! You have to fly or it's the end!
お耳チェックOK？ 方程式バインド！
Ear check OK? Equation bind!
最高！最高！最高！ 飛んでみなよフュージョン！
Awesome! Awesome! Awesome! Try to fly, fusion!
めちゃくちゃ脳内 充実するサウンズ オープンシャン！
Sounds that completely fill my brain! Open-shan!
ドッカン！ドッカン！ドッカン！
Bang! Bang! Bang!
ぽちっとぽちっとぽん！ 間違えちゃった？てへっ！
Click, click, pop! Made a mistake? Te-he!
そんなのとうに計算通り！
That was calculated long ago!
ジッケンタ！ジッケンタ！ジッケンジッケンジッケンタ！
Test subject! Test subject! Test-test-test subject!
ジッケンタ！ジッケンタ！わっふー！
Test subject! Test subject! Wah-hoo!
ジッケンタ！ジッケンタ！ジッケンジッケンジッケンタ！ジッケンタ！ジッケンタ！ジッケンタ！
Test subject! Test subject! Test-test-test subject! Test subject!
さあさあ、もっと声出せるよねー？
Come on, come on, you can make more noise, right?
じゃあ、一緒に『ジッケンタ！』って叫ぶよー！
Then, let's scream "Jikkenta!" together!
せーの、ジッケンター！
Ready, go, Jikkenta!
もーいっちょ『ジッケンタ』いくよー！
Let's go for "Jikkenta" one more time!
せーの、ジッケンター！
Ready, go, Jikkenta!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
拙者、風真いろは！いざ尋常に、勝負！
I am Kazama Iroha! Let's have a fair and square duel!
叩き切る！
I'll strike you down!
向う向うの妖精 この歌うたう
The fairy far, far away sings this song,
パートナーの眼になりたい
I want to become the eyes of my partner,
一途続く その前より
even more than before, continuing single-mindedly,
仕切った地に立ちたい
I want to stand on the ground I have conquered,
朽ちる実を芽吹かせる
making the decaying fruit sprout anew.
八百万の雨が降ろうと
Even if the rains of the eight million gods fall,
風向きの進むことなく
without the wind's direction stopping its course,
八百万の声を灯せば
if we light up the voices of the eight million gods...
由縁もありし一日の
...a single day that has its reasons...
記憶にできるから
...can be turned into a memory.
何度も弄るのか何故
Why do you tamper with it over and over?
深く沈む
Sinking deep down...
後ろ負ければ愛されないと
Believing I won't be loved if I fall behind,
日陰の刃になりたしと
I wanted to become a blade in the shadows...
狂え、荒れよ、滾れ
Go wild, rage, and boil!
酒を交わすくらい
To the point of sharing a drink,
身を切るぐらいに凪を打つ
striking a calm so intense it cuts through the flesh,
有り明けの先で
beyond the dawn.
向う向うの妖精 この歌うたう
The fairy far, far away sings this song,
同情もない
There is no sympathy,
落ちていく目
eyes falling down.
無はしょうがない
There's nothing to be done about nothingness,
もう全部塗り替えよう
let's repaint everything now.
渇目せよ
Feast your eyes!
X X X X 交差する真ん中で
X, X, X, X, right at the intersection,
X X X
世界はもう始まっている
The world has already begun!
JUMP!
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
コピュラな コピュラな なりたいダーリン
I want to be your copular, copular darling.
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
笑うのは
The ones laughing...
ホロックスで！
...will be holoX!
La-Pa-Pa-Pa...
イェーイ！
Yeeey!
ホロックスのライブが始まったぞー！
The holoX live concert has begun!
おにぎりわー！
Onigiriwa!
こんにちはー！
Hello!
こんちゃひっぴーすです！
Hello, hip peace!
全然、秘匿性のない秘匿性(笑)
There's absolutely no secrecy to our secret society (laughs).
じゃあ、自己紹介しようか？
Well, shall we introduce ourselves?
はい！
Yes!
そう！狂気の宴の始まりだー！
That's right! The banquet of madness has begun!
貴様ら、渇目せよ！
You lots, feast your eyes!
吾輩の名前はラプラス・ダークネスだ！
My name is Laplus Darknesss!
そして！
And next!
はい！皆様、待った？
Yes! Everyone, did you wait?
新しいのよ！
It's a new one!
お披露目それ？すごい、やってくれた、みんな！
Is that a debut? Wow, you guys did it!
ホロックスの女幹部、鷹嶺ルイと申します！
I am the holoX executive, Takane Lui!
待った？待った？イェーイ！
Did you wait? Did you wait? Yay!
そして！
And next!
はーい！ちょっと新しいの行きます！
Okay! I'll do a slightly new one!
あの子より！
Better than that girl!
その子より！
Better than this girl!
こよりー！
Koyori!
いけてるじゃーん！すごーい！
You guys are so good! Awesome!
ありがとう！初めてやりました！
Thank you! This is my first time doing it!
ホロックスの頭脳、博衣こよりだよ！
I am the holoX brains, Hakui Koyori!
そして！
And next!
お供たち！わかってるよね？わかってるよね？
Otomo! You know what to do, right? You know, right?
わかってるけど、じゃあ行くよ！
I know you do, so here we go!
ござるさんは？
Gozaru-san is...
かわいい！
...cute!
え、もう一回！ござるさんは？
Wait, one more time! Gozaru-san is...
かわいい！
...cute!
わ、何か内部の人間が変なこと言ってますが！
Wh- Whoa, some people inside are saying strange things, but...
ホロックスのイケメン強々カッコいい用心棒、風真隊の、風真いろはでござる！
...I'm Kazama-tai's Kazama Iroha, the handsome, strong, and cool holoX bodyguard!
ついにこの日が来てしまった
The day has finally come...
始まっちゃった
It's started!
緊張しなかった？
Weren't you nervous?
よお
Hey there.
危ない、危ない
That was close, that was close.
最初のメドレー、すごかったでしょ？
The opening medley was amazing, wasn't it?
みんな、こんな風に混ざってソロ来るって、予想出来てた？！
Did you guys expect us to mix up like that for the solos?!
ペンライト、バツ？
A cross with penlights?
そうよ、最初からクライマックス。
That's right, we hit the climax right from the start.
これぐらいの盛り上がりで待ってて。
Wait, we are starting at this level of hype?
始まったばっかだけどね。
And we've only just begun!
始まったばっかといえばさ、みんな自己紹介の時、実はもううるっと来てて...
Speaking of just beginning, during the self-introductions, everyone was actually tearing up already...
やめて、その話は！
Don't bring that up!
特にルイさんの時ね
Especially during Lui-san's part.
楽屋の時点でルイさんは...
Even in the dressing room, Lui-san was already...
いやいやいや
No, no, no.
一番早かったよね、ルイ姉。
Lui-nee was the first to tear up.
いつも、いつもルイから
It's always, always Lui...
違うのよ、花粉症！
No, it's not! It's hay fever!
ごまかさないで！
Don't try to hide it!
メンバー大好きだから...
Because I love the members so much...
泣き出した、泣き出した！
She's crying, she's crying!
泣き出してない！
I am not crying!
やめてよ、やめてよ。
Stop it, stop it.
それをみんなでいじってたのに...
We were all teasing her about it...
ここに来てみんなの笑顔を見たらさ、ちょっとみんな、うるっと来ちゃって。
But once we got here and saw everyone's smiles, we all got a bit teary-eyed.
始まる前はさ、みんなこんな感じで待ってたのに。
Before starting, we were all waiting like this...
自己紹介始まった瞬間、
But the moment self-introductions started...
ふぇぇん...みたいな、めっちゃ笑顔でふぇぇんってなって、 wagon
it was like, "Waaah!" with a big smile...
みんなの声とか音とか凄くて、みんな泣いてた。
everyone's voices and the sound were so incredible, we were all crying.
そう、うるっと来て、でも「やらなきゃ！」ってやったんだよね。
Yeah, we got teary-eyed, but then we thought, "We have to do this!" and pushed through.
やらないといけないよね。
We had to do it.
今日はかまさないといけないよね。
We have to blow them away today.
でも1曲目はかませたんじゃないか？
But didn't we blow them away with the first song?
かませてた！
We totally did!
ちょっとさ、最初の曲のメドレーのタイトル言ってやってよ。
Hey, tell them the title of that opening medley.
ちょっと待って、これ読むの？
Wait, you want me to read this?
めっちゃかっこよく言えるよ。
You can say it in a really cool way.
じゃ、頼むわ。
Alright, I'll do it.
みんな、「holoXメドレー」はみんな知ってるよね？
Everyone, you all know the "holoX Medley", right?
今日、今日のための特別なタイトルがあるから。
We have a special title just for today.
そうなのよ、叫んで。
That's right, shout it out.
いくぞ！
Here we go!
holoXメドレー、エクステンド・リミックス、みんなの必殺技詰め込んでみましたバージョン！
holoX Medley: Extended Remix — We Packed in Everyone's Signature Moves Version!
なんか、最後ちょっと...
The ending was a bit...
そのままなんだよね。
Exactly as it sounds.
無理やりじゃない？
Isn't that a bit forced?
かっけー！
Cool!
かっけー。決まったぜ。 wagon
Cool, right? Nailed it.
配信組も盛り上がってますか？
Is the stream audience hyped up too?
コメントも見えてるからね。 wagon
We can see your comments too!
コメントも「イェーイ」「うおー」しか言ってない。 wagon
The comments are just saying "Yeah!" and "Whoa!"
タイトル長いって言われてる。 wagon
They're saying the title is too long! wagon
長くないよ！ wagon
It's not long! wagon
吾輩の名前より短いじゃん。
It's shorter than my name!
それはそう。 wagon
Well, that's true.
もうみんな開演前から気づいてたと思うけど... DJ！ wagon
I think everyone noticed even before the show started, but... DJ!
DJ最高！ wagon
The DJ is the best!
落ちないようにね。 wagon
Don't fall off!
本当だよ、超高いぜ。 wagon
Seriously, it's super high up.
というわけで、 wagon
And with that,
ここから先は、本当の任務に入っていくぞ！ wagon
from here on, we're heading into the real mission!
なんですけど、ここで... wagon
But before that, we have... wagon
いやだ、俺は聞かないぞ。 wagon
No, I won't listen! wagon
お話が... wagon
An announcement... wagon
ちょっと私から言うのはあれなんで、こよりさん。 wagon
Since it's a bit awkward coming from me, Koyori-san... wagon
人の口を借りるな！ wagon,s:
Don't make others say it! wagon
はい、ではちょっと大事なお知らせです。 wagon
Alright, here's an important announcement. wagon
YouTube、TikTokライブでご覧になっている方、 wagon
To everyone watching on YouTube and TikTok Live... wagon
無料チラ見せは、ここまでとなります！ wagon
this is the end of the free preview! wagon
関係ないのに「えー」って言ってくれてる。 wagon
They're groaning "Eeeeh" even though it doesn't affect them. wagon
ですが、この後のあんなパフォーマンスや豪華な楽曲など、 wagon
But you can still make it for the upcoming performances and gorgeous songs... wagon
今からでも間に合いますので、この辺、概要欄から配信チケットを購入してください！ここ、ここ！ wagon
You can still buy streaming tickets from the description box below! Here, right here! wagon
ここ、ここ！ wagon
Right here, right here! wagon
ここです！ wagon
Right here! wagon
お前ら、 wagon
You guys... wagon
絶対買えよな！ wagon
better buy them, okay?! wagon
買った、落とした！ wagon
She dropped her hat! wagon
戻り、戻り。 wagon
Put it back, put it back. wagon
そしてこのライブの感想などはですね、ハッシュタグ「#SSholoX世界リペイント計画」でポストしてくださいね。 wagon
And please post your thoughts on this live show using the hashtag #SSholoX世界リペイント計画! wagon
お願いします。 wagon
Please do! wagon
そしてそして、配信組はいっぱいスクショ撮ってアップしてね！ wagon
And also, stream viewers, take lots of screenshots and post them! wagon
お願いします！ wagon
Please do! wagon
はい！ってことで
Yes! And with that...
じゃあここからね、さっき言った通り、本当のミッション始まりますのでね！
Now then, as we said earlier, our real mission is about to begin!
はい！
Yes!
おーい！まだ声出せるよなー！？
Hey! You can still make some noise, right?!
ここにいる全員、そして配信のみんな、覚悟はいいか！？
Everyone here, and everyone on the stream, are you ready?!
ファーストミッション、ここからが本番だ！
First Mission... this is where the real show begins!
それでは、任務続行！
Well then, mission resume!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！